listen listen listen listen fuck you
fuck you fuck up bogum
get out get out I do fuck off you fat
useless sack of fucking the Yankees
thank you do - I'd fuck off with your
pleasure Andy you're a first-class cunt
I told you I have to send that shit Hey
look there you go
that's Whistler for you yes no chef yeah
that's my ratty restaurant in Whistler
yes fuck off will you fine dining no
sure I fine fucking mess your man's
fucking consistent as pigeons shit on
Trafalgar Square
chocolate where's that I want I'll fuck
off AJP take him on yourself back to
fucking Belgium thanks fuck right off
fuck off I'm done you you you you fuck
up out of it whoo get out hey excuse me
master fuck me
how about fuck use a black jacket you
need a straitjacket oh fuck me shit
Bobby yes I'm looking for someone to
take control of this disgusting
embarrassing mess he doesn't give a fuck
he's dreaming he's standing there
twisting pants looking for his tartar
cover white-chocolate crap and he's just
running around like a toilet brush is
anyone gonna take control
medium to well and as well done well
done to you and well done to you
I can't believe just how inconsistent
you are
do me a favor you and you come upstairs
get out
I know what your game is yeah you just
want your all you let advertisers oh oh
oh sure yeah no wait spot move oh fuck
me oh gosh L this Archer fucking bimbo
come here you go for the dyeing room and
you explain to the fucking customer why
you're so shit fuck off will ya that's
right they got it's the kind of shit
you'd expect Tiger Woods to tee off we
look at it rubba rubba rubba when his
brain is cut will his black his fart
stuck to the pan yeah that's what I got
given done the fucking
let's give a big round of applause to
the captain hit an iceberg on the
fucking Titanic
what's the matter between you two
there's a language barrier addiction is
a language barrier he's speaking English
you dick I'm not mrs. Han Texas do
something yes sir you're a great fucking
talker for you're a shit cook you just
sunk your feet I didn't that madam fuck
off a kid went there with this jacket
chemically you if I tell you to get out
there I don't even fuck if you got a
tongue of your fat crack get out there
overcooked on the bottom crispy as fuck
and it looks like dandies flip-flop what
a shame Sharon in us enough fuck off and
go put some more makeup on three times
three Amanda
nine nine then give me nine fucking tops
you stupid big bitch roll
[Music]
Scott was making me look bad no fucking
salmon crispy as fuck on the bottom
because a pan you put them in when I
smoked it like unexpected a Serie B
finish okay
fuck you you're fired two salmon one tag
italian chef ramsay lost it and just
went like satan i my ass that would even
pass this fucking kitty cat fucking cat
food right then whistling meow I'm not
your fucking dog yeah you look more like
a dog than I do
fuck off with you jessalyn today is
about consistency
Brad chef are you consistently shit no
sure you're about to sing the Navy you
dickhead I don't know how to wake you up
anymore
you're like a zombie sorry chef you make
him look fucking good
Jackie wacky ru hey c'mere you sucky
wacky shack I look at me okay this is a
fucking joke
Oh chef Zaki wacky sorry stuff are just
about there chef yeah do me a favor get
out yes yeah fuck off will you get out
yes yeah upstairs get out
so Sebastian gets kicked out didn't see
that coming saxing wacky just take one
good look at yourselves in the mirror
cuz there's a fucking disgrace
let's don't burn your cooking and burn
pan you fucking dick oh my god leave it
leave it leave it fucking leave
blow firing your face you fucking donkey
hey hello come here
donkeys here we go we started come here
what is that - right why is that what is
that what is that fuck off will you fuck
off okay
that's already fucked when you roll it
looking like a pair of fucking knickers
I'm sorry new winter she's right raw
fucking bus oh my god like here comes
anything to take down no chef nothing at
all anything to say
anybody fuck off both you fuck off
upstairs five and a half minutes I'm
watching you like your fucking war I
know you're sure why I don't know yeah I
want you out you've got a pan here like
that and you've thrown lettuce on top
like that your shit
you are so shit you don't realize what
you do you've now just confirmed in my
mind you're not trustworthy so fuck you
oz it back to chef Melissa the fucking
gremlin everything she touches she
screws there you go hi guys hey I'm Adam
this is our first night
yes chef no chef yes chef no chef
fucking gremlin you do seriously
surprise me thank you sure I was hoping
you'd see that I mean I'd give it all I
got give you 110 you surprise me
- how shit you are huh Sharon you're
scaring me you don't like a female
version of fucking Hannibal Lecter put
your fucking tongue in and concentrate
yes chef Hannibal shut the fuck up just
wish you might not be so rude just lets
quill no we're on that ticket yeah
listen yes sir concentrate yes sir four
minutes in the window
yes sure one but get your lobster yes
sir one scallops yes sure now would you
like me to fucking email after your
BlackBerry no chef
move your ass yes sir you're back in the
Institute again aren't you no way
shoving that shit
big boy come on I gotta get home want to
thank you about taste taste hey I'm done
standing here with a bunch of idiots
fuck you all good luck
superstars useless oh my God Almighty
right now that's not suggest you do buy
a restaurant put one table in there any
more than that you'd be fucked first out
there it's like a plastic silicon
implant fucking bin them get rid of them
don't fuck in there
don't fucking dare Missy Missy come here
you fat mouth little stupid bitch yes
yeah you're pissing around with
something is not working yes sir I got
fucking click yes yep
it's fucking rare where's the lamb sauce
come on man I just need them oh and
listen ladies that has been 1 hour and
40 minutes for for starters and
personally I wouldn't laugh or scream or
start wetting your knickers because that
is fucking embarrassing
yes chef the customers gone customers
fucking John
[Music]
Oh schnapps
useless fucking pieces of shit till no
his crab not one of you got a ball doing
about it here you fucking up you're
cutting corners and you're slipping
big-time yeah what yeah your biggest
problem will always be the downfall your
career you're full of fucking shit every
time you got fucking something wrong you
give a bullshit fucking excuse all right
now I'm fed up with your bullshit
excuses there's really nothing that I
can do to please Chef Ramsay and I'm
slowly but surely being able to accept
their oh yes yeah you're too dangerous
to have on service I asked you what
you're doing you said you're stating
Tomatoes argued Bunch you dirty Pig get
out all the goodness is running out
because you cut through thick cunt
yeah let's just stand back and watch
that chicken and the juice piss out of
it let's seal that they're tasty it's
delicious yeah unfortunately it should
be a customer tasting it not you I think
he's tasted enough crap on top of crap
on top of crap on top of crap you're one
of the most fucking saddest I've ever
met in the fucking kitchen it takes a
little time I can't get used to this
sounds like a fucking weirdo on dr.
field man Ben that's never I'm about to
smack
there you go up up are we a fast-food
joint now oh sure
you're standing here you little balls of
fucking look you're the one that's
supposed to be supporting them yeah sure
how about supporting your fucking gun
both you sit down
hey enjoy your shit can be waiting 28
minutes per awful thank you do you do
you this offer okay where's the Belgian
brown thwack okay JP yeah open Hell's
Kitchen when you wash them then you stop
it it's stubborn it's happening you
don't perform an appendicitis you fuck
what do we wait now what do we got
what are we waiting on I'm waiting on
some fucking talents there chef it's a
fucking joke
let's go horrendous fuck off watch my
stuff please get in there he was
Madam's a Milo Milo yes take your jacket
off and fucker miss the bus and
Wellington now your cousin unload bits
of chicken nugget and frying them off
Mischa you fucking donkey why put them
on a dirty try chef on because I was
doing Wellington on them before they
could not find any more not good enough
for you no it's not yes it it's not I
don't want to do it this eternity Pig
yeah sure clean the fucking tray yeah
chef one more and your fucking history
teacher dead oh if I was you I'd dig
deep touch your ball and wake up maybe
you wonder why I go a little bit fucking
dude Ali it's in front of you just all
taking place naturally ah fuck me fuck
me fuck me fuck me fuck me
every fucking table I'm getting screwed
area let's go we're getting fucked cuz
her fucking lambs already
all of hearing come here right now come
here chef Smith screaming his head off
all night so right now I'm scared
shitless now I'm fucking serious I am
NOT gonna bust my balls to send one that
one chicken one bat one halibut and then
the rest of the fucking table either you
get it together right now or fuck off
Hey you you you fuck off out of it we'll
finish your service telling you if you
don't get out I'll drag you out just as
the door videos recipes demos is a
fucking joke
well I have a problem I have a big
fucking problem
this is wrong oh this is wrong not again
damn it this can't be happening I'm all
right it's just get three more going put
him in the oven it's fuck we're going
down in flames
Titanic ain't got shit on us
[Music]
you you do here you get out get the fuck
out of it
I'm calling out orders you're confused
you're complete and you're fucking on
the end of your dish let's see John do
one table of time reheating spinach
yes chef like a chef well wake up yes
sir wake up yes goodness finish to order
your lazy cow Chef Ramsay needs to learn
how to show some respect especially with
our beer working hard stewed spinach
yeah rabbit fur fuck you honestly the
first time my fucking cooking career
yeah I'm in a kitchen with Muppets thank
you sir take that yeah do me a favor
fuck off get out answer the fucking
dorms forget your fucking hair done
get out of my kitchen first thing of the
blue team on resulting wants dollars one
squab one spaghetti
yes yeah I'm sorry chef can you get up
come on who's that yeah let me repeat it
fuck yourself yes sir
he brings that pissing over and the big
surprise is the fucking bass is fucking
what the fuck is going on that's what he
gave you oh that was folded like that to
make it look like a filling mean I tried
to push it down chef yes filet mignon
yeah chef look at it you cut them you
can fuck off no I will not get them why
are you gonna cut them then because if I
cut them all the juice will come out you
I because of just why it won't be juicy
holy look at that like a Bisons penis
why is that shit leave it chef yes when
you go like this you go I'm good I'm
good I'm bringing her targum fucking
shit are ya sure you get fucking pure a
hot come on please I can't I don't know
where to go now I've had some tough
nights in my life but not over a fucking
fried egg what's going through your mind
now he's still gonna fuckin butcher me
and slice me and serve shit to them no
chef where's your fight man it's yours
music I've got it chef then wake up you
donut yeah sure know my name because
it's on my shirt get the fucking donkey
out of there you start showing me you
don't care about my fucking ears
I'm gonna start showing you that I don't
care about you yes yo Sam can no one
make a fucking risotto part of the blue
team
I'd have they're off the fucking
appetizers I'll put on the garnish and
somewhere the pair of balls would step
up and take over that fucking mess all
of you come here
just look
just look at the fucking mess in here
the shit the disarray the
disorganization and look look look look
at the men what's wrong with you look at
me how you learn your England case look
at my fucking eyes I'm talking Jesus
what's wrong with you I'm trying to work
chair I'm trying to communicate
wake up yes you what's wrong with you
nothing
yeah get a grip yeah you you made bar
for the shill coming out and you look
halibuts stuck to the past you fucking
took me again next time you go for an
early bath yes a big one in the hot tub
[Music]
right well I'll get you more pumpkin
I'll Ram it right up your fucking ass
which I get whole or diced take this
useless Brigade around every freaking
table and I want a sincere apology on
the back of your crap performance piss
off every one of them ladies yes that
was the first useful thing you have done
tonight it's also the last get out of
here
all of you and hang your heads in shame
because you absolutely suck piss off
embarrassing and all family nines
you totally don't care about the
children